( BOTH panting )
( whooping )
Oh , yeah !
WOMAN : Okay , you 're great .
You got the line ?
Yeah . Come on up , slowpoke .
( panting )
( screaming )
Help !
You okay ? You know , we 're 50 miles from anybody .
Who are you screaming for ?
You .
Come on .
Just pull me up !
Rich ?
Just pull me up .
All rig ht , don 't be a dick , Richie. I need a pull .
Rich ?
( GASPS )
What ...
( WHlMPERlNG )
( screaming )
( SCREAMS )
( MAN laughing MAN lACALLY )
( WHlMPERlNG )
( SCREAMS )
( screaming )
( RADIO STATIC )
MAN 1 ON RADIO : When you plant a seed into your own kin , you anger God .
MAN 2 : ... still have not been able to locate the two missing
Bluefield State College students .
Richard Stoker and Halley Smith have been missing since last Monday
after failing to return from a weekend of rock ...
( HALLO WEEN playing )
( singing ) There 's a place you might wanna go
lt 's right up my street
You might look and see the light shining
( siren wailing )
It 's Halloween
He said ...
( TURNS OFF engine )
( CAR HORN SHONKlNG )
( COUNTRY music playing ON radio )
( GASPS )
Hey . How are you doing ?
Do you have any idea what 's going on up here ?
Tractor jackknifed about five mileup .
Spilled chemicals and shit all over the road .
Any idea how long it 'll take to clean up ?
Couple of hours .
Couple of hours ?
You in a hurry ?
Yeah . I need to get to Raleigh tonight .
What you ought to do is get back in your car ...
Mm m-h m m .
... fix your hair a couple hundred more ti mes ...
Thank you .
( CAR HORN honking )
Hey , Doris . This is Chris Flynn .
I have a 7 : 00p.m . interview with Mr.Keller.
I 'm running about 30 minutes late .
( PHONE BEEPS ) I was wondering if you could ...
Hello ? Hello ?
I 'm not gonna make this .
( GRUNTS in frustration )
Excuse me , sir . Do you have a pay phone ?
This one 's not working . Do you have another phone I could use ?
Long distance ?
What isn 't long distance from here , right ?
You cutting wise with me , son ?
No , sir , I 'm j ust ... I 'm running behind , and I really need to make a call .
That one there is my only phone .
Right .
Well , the highway 's really jammed up .
Do you know of another route heading south ?
No . No .
Why is this Bear Mountain Road dotted like this ?
Dirt . Dirt road ?
Afraid they ain 't got around to paving it yet .
It looks like it runs into the highway about 15 , 20 miles. ls that right ?
If you say so .
It could work . Thank you very much .
You take care , okay ?
You 're the one that gonna need to take care .
( lF ONLY playing )
( singing ) lf it gets you down , well , I don 't want it
I don 't want it
( TRACK skipping )
Only , if only
Only was nothing at all
( panting )
EVAN : We just got nailed , man !
SCOTT : Jesus Christ ! FRANClNE : Shit !
Goddamn drunkass hillbilly !
Hey . Hey , you all right ?
I 'm so sorry. I just ... SCOTT : Yeah .
Jesus . I was just coming around the bend .
I didn 't even see ... I got distracted .
My God , you could 've died !
Are you guys all okay ?
Yeah , yeah . You wanna sit down ?
You might be in a state of shock or something .
What the hell were you doing driving so goddamn fast for ?
All right , all right .
Why was your truck parked in the middle of the road ?
Because we blew out our tires , asshole !
Hey , look , I 'll pay for whatever damage was done ...
You 're damn right you 're gonna pay . That 's my mom 's car .
All right , Frannie . The man said he 'd pay for ...
Looks like you killed my bike here , too .
I 'm sorry. I ... How did you blow out your tires ?
Someone left some barbed wire in the middle of the road .
I can 't believe someone just dropped it there .
Nobody dropped anything .
I just found this tied to a tree back there . Somebody did this .
SCOTT : Southern hospitality at its finest .
FRANClNE : Red neck assholes .
Look , I 'm gonna go try and find a phone .
I think I saw a gas station like a couple miles back .
I 'm gonna come with you .
There is no phone . I was just there .
Look , why don 't we just wait for someone else to come along ?
What , like Speed Racer here ?
FRANClNE : Look , I 'm not going anywhere .
Okay , you guys go , and , I don 't know , we 'll just stay here , Francine , and ...
jessie : And get high .
EVAN : Yeah . So what ?
SCOTT : Careful . They don 't like stoners .
FRANClNE : Who are you calling a stoner ?
Your mom .
Hey , what 's your name ?
ChrisFlynn .
You hurt , ChrisFlynn ?
No , I 'm fine . Good .
'Cause you 're the mule .
SCOTT : Oh , no .
You know , I can carry that . You just had the whole car accident thing .
FRANClNE : Yeah , we 'll just stay here and maybe get hit again .
jessie : Are you guys sure you 're cool ?
EVAN : Yeah .
Yeah , we 'll be just fine . Thank you .
Bet you will .
Yeah , smoke it up there , Skippy .
( LAUGHS )
Yeah , have fun .
SCOTT : I don 't fucking believe this .
Your mom 's gonna kick your ass .
God , I can not get it out of my head what just happened .
Are you sure you 're all right ? Yeah ?
Yeah . I 'm fine .
What are you guys doing out here ?
Camping . I don 't know . Actually , we 're lost .
You know , a lot of people say ,
who have been through similar traumatic experiences ,
that the following moments kind of feel like you 're moving kind of in slow motion .
Do you feel like that ? No .
I should tell you that my voice is fairly low in normal speed .
( LAUGHS )
EVAN : Pretty good .
( FRANClNE COUGHS )
FRANClNE : Where 'd you get this ?
I got it out of my dad 's room , actually .
You can finish it .
EVAN : I can 't believe they called us stoners .
Dickheads .
CARLY : Are you sure you know where we 're going ?
chris : Yeah . There was a map at the gas station .
CARLY : I 'm so tired already . I 'm starving , and I 'm being eaten by ants .
Are there any on my back ?
No , nothing there . Hey-ho ! I call it , squirrel .
Well , you said you were hungry , Carly .
I don 't think it 's a squirrel .
It 's a mink .
Really ? How do you know ?
Probably ran over it .
In medical school , they make you work on animal cadavers
before you get to the real thing .
It 's a mink .
SCOTT : It 's a mink ?
I need to be in Raleigh by 7 : 00 .
Mm m . Better get a move on , then .
You know , we should 've just taken her to New York .
No . You know how she loves this outdoor stuff .
Yeah .
If you ask me , though , nature sucks .
Well , the next time she gets dumped , we 'll take her to New York .
Drop your pants .
What ?
When do people always show up , Evan ?
What are we doing ?
Consider it an experiment in probability theory .
Really ?
I love you .
I know .
Now get them trousers off , boy . Don 't be a sissy .
All right .
SCOTT : You know , baby , I 've been thinking about this whole wedding thing ,
and I think we should take a trip down to Mexico .
I 'm talking about a long weekend , margaritas ,
the two of us on a beach alone , sunset .
And , you know , I 'm talking about just , just eloping .
You know what I mean ?
Okay . Wait a second .
You wanna know what I think ?
Yes , please .
I think if you ever want to get in my pants again ...
Affirmative .
... that 's the last time you use the " E " word .
Okay ? Okay .
Yeah , it 's a disgusting word .
Hey , guys , hold on .
Hey , is anyone up there ?
Hello !
There must be people nearby .
Anyone up there ?
Somebody had to start it .
Let 's keep moving .
Hello ?
Freaky .
Look at this . It 's fucked !
Nothing . Nothing .
Hey , did you find anything to eat ? They took all my PowerBars .
No . No . Sorry .
Damn it . Scott and Carly took all our frigging sunscreen .
Does he have any good CDs ?
Mm m-m m m .
( RUSTLlNG ) Definitely not .
You know , I think this guy must be some kind of doctor .
Maybe we could get him to write us some prescriptions when he gets back .
( sighs )
He doesn 't have any smokes , either .
Almost out .
Evan ?
Evan ? Where are you ?
Hey , baby , what are you doing ?
I 'm just am using myself .
You getting anything there , chatty ?
No , nothing . I 'm gonna miss this thing .
Why didn 't you just fly ?
I put all of my money into that car back there .
SCOTT : Okay , forget eloping , but there is an idea
I think we should discuss about the band for our wedding .
I think we should hire , you know , a Frank Sinatra-type lead singer for the band
as opposed to a James Brown-type lead singer ,
because , you know , really , let 's be honest , there 's only one James Brown ,
and , you know , a faux James Brown is really quite intolerable .
Evan ? Where are you ?
You pissing or something ?
Evan ?
( RUSTLlNG )
You know , plus he 'd be grinding his hips , and my grand mother would be ,
yes , revolted but also strangely fascinated
in a completely disturbing way and ...
Baby ?
Carly , I was kidding .
Carly ?
( bird CAWS )
FRANClNE : Evan ?
( files buzzing )
( WHlMPERlNG )
( gasping )
( screaming )
Sweetheart ? Hey , guys , hold up !
Guys , hold up for a second , allright ?
Baby , seriously , this isn 't funny .
( laughing ) Jesus . God ! Baby !
Oh ! I 'm so sorry .
I could 've killed you , woman . I 'm extremely dangerous .
You wanna know why I love you so much ?
Because you 're so fun to play with .
is that why you love me ?
That really scared me , baby . I 'm sorry .
That really scared me . Would you not do that ?
chris : ( echoing ) Hello !
Hello !
There 's nothing like stating the obvious , huh ?
( laughing )
Hey , baby , look at this .
( whooping )
Hey , Carly , I think this would be a good time
for you to confront your fear of heights !
CARLY : Don 't !
Okay , that is not funny .
Look who 's scared now .
Sorry . Whatever .
Just get me to a motel room , run me a very hot bath ,
and be prepared to provide me with a lot of orgasms .
I think they need to be alone .
What do you expect ? They just got engaged .
They 're happy . It 's a hard thing to find .
Yeah .
Got it ? Limber tongue . Got it .
You 're stupid .
jessie : Maybe we shouldn 't have left Francine and Evan .
chris : Don 't worry . They 're fine .
You guys okay ? SCOTT : Super .
jessie : Well , wait , guys . This road isn 't on here .
CARLY : That 's because you don 't have the Red neck World Atlas .
( EXCLAlMlNG )
SCOTT : I think we 've just been saved , kids .
( whooping ) Can I get a ...
( SCOTT LAUGHS )
Make this quick .
SCOTT : Actually , maybe we should keep walking .
CARLY : What ? The next house is gonna have a white picket fence ?
Yeah , if there is a next house .
Hey . What ?
Hello ?
All right , this isn 't right .
Hello ? Anybody home ?
( CHlMES ringing )
Baby , could you ...
Hey , hey , what are you doing ?
I was gonna see if they had a phone . You guys can wait out here if you want .
You can 't just go barging into someone 's house like that .
Yeah because , you know , I 'm just thinking ,
West Virginia , trespassing , not a great combination .
Look , I need to pee .
Well , I need to remind you of a little movie called Deliverance .
Guys , we got two wrecked cars. I mean , we really need a phone .
Hello ?
Carly .
( files buzzing )
SCOTT : What the fuck ?
jessie : Let 's just do what we gotta do and get out of here .
CARLY : Hey , I am not sensing a phone here .
Hello !
Okay , who lives here ?
CARLY : I don 't know , but can you help me find a bathroom ?
Baby , I think this is the bathroom .
( sighs )
SCOTT : ( GROANS ) Fuck .
chris : Oh , my God . Look at this place .
SCOTT : Seriously , guys , I think we should go .
CARLY : Okay , just help me find the bathroom . Then we 'll go .
Baby , what if this place belongs to some kind of cult ?
Actually , I reading Newsweek how economically-depressed places
are like breeding grounds for all kinds of apocalyptic visionaries .
Order of the Solar Temple , Jom bola ,
Church of the Lamb of God , the Chijon Family .
Remember them ? Not nice people . Hey , brainiac !
( SHUSHlNG )
All right . Maybe that door .
( CARLY exclaims )
SCOTT : Jesus Christ ! CARLY : You 're fine .
chris : You okay ? It 's just a paddle .
It 's all right .
CARLY : Whoa !
God , look at this place .
Yeah . It 's like the garage sale from hell .
CARLY : Jesus .
( music BOX playing )
CARLY : Can you believe this ?
SCOTT : Jesus , these guys are ripping people off .
jessie : Chris . Mm m-h m m .
I think we should leave .
SCOTT : This is kind of creepy , actually .
Yeah , this is it . Okay . Be quick .
Okay .
All right ? Two minutes .
All right ? I 'll be here .
( sighs )
( MOTOR running )
( files buzzing )
( GROANS )
CARLY : Ew !
( MOTOR STOPS )
jessie : Guys , guys , check this out .
Oh , no .
Oh , God . Oh , God . Scott . Scott !
( GASPS )
Scott , we have to go now !
Jess ! Jessie ! Jess !
jessie : Hey ! Guys , what is it ?
We need to get back to your friends .
What about a phone ? There is no phone .
SCOTT : Shit !
chris : There 's a back door . I saw a back door . Come on .
Go ! jessie : Go , go !
Okay , hurry . Shit !
CARLY : Shit ! No !
( GRUNTlNG )
Scott ! Scott ! It 's not gonna budge ! Come on !
( MEN muttering )
( MAN breathing heavily )
( MAN muttering )
( stifled WHlMPERlNG )
( WHlMPERlNG )
( MAN GRUNTlNG )
( MOANlNG )
( files buzzing )
( CLATTERlNG )
( WHlMPERlNG )
( MAN laughing MAN lACALLY )
( files buzzing )
( MAN snoring )
( MAN wheezing )
( JESSlE GASPS )
( SNORlNG continues )
( CLATTERlNG )
( GASPS )
( files buzzing )
( SNORlNG )
Go .
( MOUTHlNG )
Go ! Go !
Go ! Go ! Go , baby ! Go ! Go !
Go , you guys ! Run !
SCOTT : Go quickly . Come on .
Come on ! Come on !
( TRUCK engine starting )
( GASPS )
( MEN whooping )
( pounding )
Where are they going ? I don 't know .
Jesus , did that really just happen ?
Do you think Evan 's okay ?
( CARLY GROANS )
Baby .
( crying ) I can 't. I can 't .
Carly , come on ! Get up !
You didn 't see what they did to Francine .
You didn 't see what we saw !
Carly ! Carly ! Carly ! Sweet pea !
Look at me . We are gonna get out of this , I swear to you .
We are . Okay ? We 're gonna find a road . We 're gonna get to a town .
And we 're going home . We 're gonna get married . All right ?
And we are never going into the woods again .
All right ? chris : We gotta go .
Come on . This way ! Let 's go ! Come on !
What is this ?
chris : Jesus .
All these people .
Baby . Fuck .
CARLY : How can they do this ? I don 't understand .
How 'd they get away with this ?
Oh , my God . All these people .
chris : Maybe one of them still runs . Look for keys .
SCOTT : None of these cars are gonna run .
Come on . Look at them . Oh , fuck .
( TRUCK approaching )
Get down ! Get down !
SCOTT : Oh , sh it . CARLY : What ?
( laughing MAN lACALLY )
( sniffing )
What do we do ?
They left their truck running . jessie : So ?
We gotta take it .
jessie : How are we supposed to do that ?
One of us leads them in the wrong direction
and the rest commandeer the truck so they 'll run for the runner .
It 's a classic military move .
jessie : Who goes ? Me .
Hey ! Hey ! Hey ! Hey !
Over here !
( GROANS )
( whooping )
( GRUNTlNG )
SCOTT : Oh , shit . Oh , God . Oh , God .
( MAN laughing ) Go !
Listen , help him get to the truck . I 'll meet you there .
I love you . I love you .
Fuckers ! Asshole motherfuckers !
Assholes !
( BOTH gasping )
( SHUSHlNG ) He 's okay .
( laughing MAN lACALLY )
( GRUNTS )
Come on .
Here , here . You 're okay .
chris : Go ahead . Go , go , go . Go to the truck .
( screaming )
Go . Come on . We gotta go .
We gotta go . Come on ! I can 't !
I can 't ! Come on !
jessie : Carly , get in !
( GUN SHOT )
( laughing MAN lACALLY )
( GUN SHOTS CONTlUE )
We gotta find Scott ! We have to find Scott !
( panting )
Where is he ? Where is he ?
There he is ! There he is ! There he is ! Scott !
Run , Scott ! We 're over here ! Scott !
jessie : Scott ! Come on ! Scott , let 's go !
jessie : Come on !
CARLY : Come on !
( GASPS )
Come on , Scott ! Scott !
chris : Let 's go !
Scott , come on ! Come on , Scott !
( WHOOSHlNG )
CARLY : Come on , Scott ! Scott ! Scott ! What are you doing ?
Scott , what 's wrong ? Scott ! Scott !
Scott ! No !
( gasping )
No !
Let go of me ! Let me go !
Scott !
( crying ) No !
Drive ! Drive !
No ! Drive !
( MAN whooping )
( crying )
Oh , God !
What 's happening ?
( FOOTSTEPS approaching )
( laughing )
( crying ) Oh , God , what 's happening ?
Jess , please , can we go back ? Please .
Carly , we have to keep going . Okay ?
Scott .
jessie : Are you sure this is the road from that map ?
chris : It 's gotta go somewhere .
This better get us out of here .
chris : Shit .
Shit . Come on .
( GRUNTS )
chris : Back it up .
jessie : Come on !
It 's not gonna go any farther . Come on . Let 's get out .
Damn it .
We gotta find out where we are .
The highest ridge is up there . Come on .
What 's the point ? They 're gonna find us anyway .
Come on . Let 's go , Carly .
No. lf he 's going , I 'm not . He got us into this .
Carly , look at me , okay ? Scott died protecting us .
We need to keep ourselves alive , or it was for nothing . Okay ?
We 're all in this together , Carl .
Come on .
( crying ) I want him back .
I know , I know .
( GRUNTlNG )
Carl , look at me . Okay ? Look .
We 're gonna stay alive . We 're gonna get out of this .
We 're gonna get out of these woods , find the police ,
and we 're gonna make sure those motherfucks are punished for this . Okay ?
Carly .
Come on , Carly . You can do it .
It 's gonna get dark soon . Come on .
We need to find that road quick .
I know .
( GRUNTlNG )
jessie : Just a little bit farther .
( JESSlE SCREAMS )
jessie : Chris !
It 's a bear trap .
( laughing )
( LAUGHTE RECHOlNG )
( GRUNTlNG )
What 's up ?
I gotta rest .
( GRUNTS )
CARLY : Hey , guys .
Look .
Oh , my God .
It 's a watchtower .
( SHUSHlNG ) Hello ! is anyone up there ?
I don 't th i n k anyone 's up there .
Doesn 't matter .
It may have a phone or a radio . Maybe we can see the road .
You okay ?
( GRUNTlNG )
Come on .
Guys , I don 't see any roads or towns out there .
Let 's not stand by the window . They might see us .
Hey . We 're all gonna die .
Carly , I need you to come help me look around , please .
jessie : Hey , Chris .
Jess . Thanks .
( groaning )
Oh , my God . It 's a radio .
chris : Thing looks prehistoric .
Do you know how to use this ?
Let me try .
CARLY : It could still work . chris : Don 't move anything .
Just keep it on the frequency they had it on .
Can anybody hear me ? We have an emergency . Can anybody hear me ?
Say " mayday . "
Look , we have a huge emergency . Please , does anybody hear me ?
Someone is injured . We need help .
Hello .
Please , is anybody out there that can hear me ? Hello .
No .
Get down . Cover the I ig ht .
( SHUSHlNG )
( whispering ) I think they 're passing us .
( FEEDBACK screeching )
( GRUNTlNG )
MAN ON radio : This is Ranger Base Emergency . Do you copy ?
What is your position ? Over .
Do you copy ? What is your position ? Over .
( SHUSHlNG ) I don 't know my position . Just help us .
MAN ON radio : I need another copy of that. I repeat , what is your position ?
They 're coming .
( GRUNTlNG )
We don 't know our position . We 're in a watchtower .
We must be north of Bear Mountain Road .
Someone is trying to kill us ! Please !
They 've murdered our friends . They 're after us right now .
MAN ON radio : I ' m having some trouble hearing you .
If you 're in the tower , stay up there . Do you copy ?
Yes , yes , we copy ! Just hurry , please ! Th is is an emergency !
Help me move this . Come on ! Come on !
We 'll come to you . Do you copy ?
They 're after us ! Someone 's been shot !
Our friends have been killed , and we need help ! Please !
Fuck !
( CARLY SCREAMS )
( MAN screaming )
What are they doing ?
I don 't know .
I think they 're going down .
Jess .
Hello ? Hello ? is anybody there ? Can you hear us ? Hello ?
( MAN laughing MAN lACALLY )
CARLY : Jesus , what are they doing ?
We 're on fire .
They 're trying to burn us out .
Oh , my God .
chris : Carly !
chris : Come here .
Let go of me ! Let go !
I 'd rather jump than burn to death !
( CARLY sobbing )
jessie : Calm down .
You 're right .
What ? She 's right .
We have to jump . Those branches are only a few feet down .
That 's more like 20 feet .
Look , Jessie , I don 't want to burn to death ,
and I don 't want to be chopped up into pieces .
We can do th is . I 'l I go first .
jessie : Chris . Hey .
( GRUNTlNG )
( GLASS breaking )
Chris ! Chris !
( SCREAMS )
Help ! Chris .
( GRUNTlNG )
( panting )
You okay ?
Do you think they saw us ?
I don 't know .
( GASPS )
( whispering ) We gotta move . Come on .
Shit . Shit .
( MAN shouting )
Carly , come on .
( MAN continues shouting )
( GRUNTlNG )
( GASPS )
I can do this . I can do this . I can do this .
I can ... I can do th is .
( SCREAMS )
( stifled sobbing )
( BODY THUDDlNG )
( clicking TONGUE )
Come on . Come on .
All right .
( MAN shouting )
He 's coming .
I know. I have a plan . Come on .
( MEN whooping )
Jessie , this way .
( GRUNTlNG )
Can you hold th is ? Why ?
'Cause we 're gonna knock th is fucker out of the tree . Can you hold it ?
Yeah .
Allright . Don 't let go until I say so . Okay ?
Where are you going ?
I 'm gonna make sure he comes this way .
No . You can 't move as quick as I can .
Jessie . Jessie .
I 'm right here ! Come and get me !
Where are you ?
Here I am !
( GASPS )
( MAN laughing )
( GRUNTlNG )
( GASPS )
( BLAD ESCRAPING )
( clicking TONGUE )
Hey !
( screaming )
( MEN muttering )
( yelling )
Sorry about your friends .
Last Friday I came home , and there 's a message on my machine
from my boyfriend , who says that we shouldn 't be together anymore .
With in 20 minutes of me telling Carly ,
she had Scott and Evan and Francine
all blowing off work this week to take me out here .
That 's just the kind of friends they were .
And now they 're dead .
It 's not your fault .
It 's not .
( sobbing )
They 're here .
( panting )
No , they 're not . You were dreaming .
I wish .
How 's your leg ? It hurts .
Which is good . If it didn 't hurt ... Road .
What ? Road . Look .
We gotta get down there .
Take that slope right there .
I can 't believe it .
How are we gonna get you down ?
I 'l I get down ...
Chris ! Go !
( yelling )
Chris ! No ! Chris ! No !
Chris ! Chris !
Chris ! Chris ! Get off of me !
( JESSlE screaming ) Jessie !
Jessie !
Hey , stop ! Oh , thank God .
Are you crazy ?
They took her . Come on . We gotta ... Calm down .
Just calm down . We gotta move .
Are you one of them folks who called me from the fire tower ?
I 've been looking for you . Will you shut up and listen ?
People are dead . Dead ? What people ?
( GASPS )
( sniffing )
( engine starting )
( JESSlE screaming )
No !
No .
Mm m .
Help me , please . I 'm sorry. I 'm sorry .
I 'm sorry . Yeah ? Can you help me ?
Please help me .
( sobbing ) No !
No !
( CAR approaching )
( JESSlE screaming )
( sobbing )
Somebody , help me !
No !
( GRUNTlNG )
( crying )
( muttering )
Help me .
( GRUNTlNG )
( yelling )
( EXCLAlMlNG )
You 're okay . Come on .
Just stay with me . You 're all right . Come on . It 's okay .
Keep looking at me . All right ? You 're okay .
Thank you .
Shh . Everything 's okay .
Chris !
( GRUNTlNG )
( choking )
( yelling )
Chris !
( GROANS )
( TlTTE ring )
( laughing )
( choking )
( YELLS )
( MAN wheezing )
Chris .
( groaning )
( screaming )
Get the fuck off of me !
Shoot them .
I only got one shot left .
Come on , you motherfuckers . Just die .
( indistinct chattering ON radio )
( yelling )
( MAN laughing MAN lACALLY )
( wish I MAY playing )
( singing ) Shoves me under you again
I can 't wait for this to end
Sober , empty in the head
I know I can never win
Why should I have to wait ?
Or I 'll just look the other way
We left this land of shiny lights
I wish I may , I wish I might
When all these dreams have come to end
You wish you were You 're not my friend
Oh
We left this land of shiny lights
I wish I may , I wish I might
When all these dreams have come to end
You wish you were You 're not my friend
You said you 'd love to see the end
The long , hard road that I have been
When all these dreams have come to end
You wish you were You 're not my friend
Bright
Eyes
Shine
Through